A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor James McDowell, 1843-1845
Library of Virginia
- Executive Papers of Governor James McDowell, 1843-1845., Extent: 9 boxes. (Box 1-9)
  - 1844
    - October
      - 1-15 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - 16-31 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - November
      - 1-13 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - 14-19 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - 20-30 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - December
      - 1-15 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - 16-30 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1845
    - January
      - 1-10 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - 11-20 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - 21-31 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - February
      - 1-15 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - 17-28 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - March
      - 1-15 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - 17-31 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - April
      - 1-18 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - 19-30 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - May
      - 1-15 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - 17-31 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - June
      - 2-14 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - 16-30 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - July
      - 1-15 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - 16-31 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - August (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - September (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - October
      - 2-15 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - 16-31 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - November
      - 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - 11-20 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - 21-30 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - December
      - 1-15 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - 16-31 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Oversized (Clamshell Box)
  - 1843
    - Feb. 7 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Apr. 22 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Aug. 7 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Aug. 18 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Sept. 8 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Nov. 25 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1844
    - Apr. 29 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - May 8 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - June 25 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1845
    - Apr. 5 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - May 12 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Sept. 16 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Oct. 2 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Oct. 14 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Oct. 18 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Nov. 1 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Nov. 3 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Nov. 19 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Nov. 19 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Nov. 24 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Oversized (Newspaper Box)
  - 1843
    - July 11 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Aug. 29 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sept. 12 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1844
    - Jan. 12 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Feb. 4 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Apr. 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Apr. 23 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Apr. 24 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Apr. 26 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - May 13 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - June 12 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - June 20 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - July 28 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Sept. 9 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Oct. 6 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Dec. 17 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 1845
    - Feb. 18 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Mar. 29 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Apr. 3 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Apr. 6 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Apr. 7 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - May 3 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - May 19 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - June 5 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Oct. 27 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Nov. 4 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Nov. 29 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Dec. 8 (Box 9, Folder 28)